<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anson MacKeracher</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Anson MacKeracher</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 09:46:08 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Shotify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/introducing-shotify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 09:46:08 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/introducing-shotify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I often want to share small bits of code that are clean, syntax&#xA;highlighted, and ready for a blog post or a quick message to a&#xA;friend. There are plenty of tools for this, but none with the tight&#xA;editor integration I wanted.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, I built one: &lt;a href=&#34;https://shotify.codes&#34;&gt;Shotify&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s what it produces:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;figure class=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;img-container&#34; &gt;&#xA;        &lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; alt=&#34;Shotify Screenshot&#34; src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/shotify-screenshot.png&#34; &gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shotify currently supports Emacs (my baby), VS Code, Neovim, and the&#xA;CLI, and is available as an &lt;code&gt;npm&lt;/code&gt; package for integrating into your own&#xA;tools.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Beginnings</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/new-beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/new-beginnings/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025, year of the Linux Desktop</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-year-of-the-desktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-year-of-the-desktop/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The year: 2025. The situation: installing Linux on a desktop&#xA;computer. The expectations: high. The result: utter disappointment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No disrespect to the incredibly talented and hardworking folks who&#xA;have created and continue to maintain Linux. It&amp;rsquo;s truly a modern&#xA;wonder of the world, that a free and open-source operating system of&#xA;such high quality exists. I use it everywhere on the server. Linux&#xA;runs on everything from toasters to spaceships.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Failure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/on-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/on-failure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You can’t pick yourself up from failure if you never truly tried.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We learn from failure. Real failure. Where you tried so hard, the&#xA;hardest you could, and you &lt;strong&gt;still&lt;/strong&gt; failed. If we half-ass something,&#xA;and fail, we have an excuse: didn’t try. If we succeed, we reinforce&#xA;that it’s acceptable to half-ass things. Either way we learn the wrong&#xA;lesson.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I get it. Things are scary, and failure hurts. Trying hard and not&#xA;achieving your goal comes with crushing disappointment. But the key is&#xA;to suffer through that and grow from it. That’s how you get&#xA;better. Trying hard means &lt;em&gt;necessarily&lt;/em&gt; that you will fail. Failure is&#xA;the &lt;code&gt;yin&lt;/code&gt; to trying hard&amp;rsquo;s &lt;code&gt;yang&lt;/code&gt;. In the wise words of my father, &amp;ldquo;You&#xA;ain&amp;rsquo;t skiing unless you&amp;rsquo;re falling.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being an Early Employee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/being-an-early-employee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/being-an-early-employee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve held a variety of roles at organizations of different sizes, but by far the most success I&amp;rsquo;ve experienced is in the environment of an early-stage, fast-growing startup company. It&amp;rsquo;s an exciting place to operate, the momentum and fast pace feels amazing to be around. The sense of progress and &amp;ldquo;building something&amp;rdquo; is palpable, optimism is in the air.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course, like all things in life, there&amp;rsquo;s a trade-off. A fast pace means high pressure. Momentum means higher expectations. Excitement also means uncertainty. Potential for huge wins necessarily means potential for huge loss.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspire GPT</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/go-inspire-gpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/go-inspire-gpt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ChatGPT has people very excited. Academics are imagining their hard-wrought papers being generated with a simple prompt. Programmers are watching machines begin to write their own code. Writers and creatives are staring at the results of a ChatGPT prompt with amazement, delight, and terror.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AI has arrived. Not the way that Hollywood said it would, but in the way that all magnificent human inventions happen: gradually, over time, with the participation of countless individuals. We did it. We can&amp;rsquo;t put the genie back in the bottle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
